The awesomest love story ever told.
Valley Girl is a comedy, romance, music film directed by Rachel Lee Goldenberg.
Set to a new wave '80s soundtrack, Julie, a girl from the
valley, meets Randy, a punk from the city.
They are from different worlds and find love.
Somehow they need to stay together in spite of her trendy, shallow friends.
Julie Richman, played by Jessica Rothe.
Randy, played by Josh Whitehouse.
Stacey, played by Jessie Ennis.
Loryn, played by Ashleigh Murray.
Karen, played by Chloe Bennet.
Mickey, played by Logan Paul.
Valley Girl is a 2020 American jukebox musical romantic comedy film directed by Rachel Lee Goldenberg, written by Amy
Talkington from a story by Wayne Crawford and Andrew Lane, and produced by Matt Smith and Steven J.
It is a remake of the 1983 film of the same name and stars Jessica
Rothe, Josh Whitehouse, Logan Paul, and Judy Greer.
The film follows Julie Richman, a Valley girl, who falls in love
with Randy, a rebellious punk, during the early 1980s.
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer first announced a musical remake in February 2012, but it was halted until November
2016 when Goldenberg joined the project as director and Rothe was cast in the lead role.
Casting announcements continued until May 2017 and principal
photography began that same month, taking place in Los Angeles.
Following the completion of filming, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer
scheduled the film for release on June 29, 2018.
However, the film was delayed following controversies
surrounding Logan Paul, who portrayed Mickey.
Valley Girl was released simultaneously through video on demand and in select
drive-in theaters on May 8, 2020, by United Artists Releasing.
It was initially set to receive a wide theatrical release on the same date, but
these plans were cancelled because of the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, with praise for the soundtrack, acting,
and tone, though many deemed it to be inferior to the original film.
The film explores themes of high school, musical, romcom, remake, mall.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.